In the 2025.2 version, we have introduced a major update for the new drawing library.
In the previous version, the new drawing library can only exist in the form of a suspended window, and the 2025.2 line is available for both options.
You can keep the original form of the drawing library, or you can choose to stop it at the side of the column.
After clicking the drawing library icon, the drawing library will be randomly opened in the form of a suspended window.
To stop the drawing library, you need to click the stop icon in the upper right corner of the drawing library. The drawing library will automatically stop at the left side of the screen column.
You can also choose to stop the drawing library at the right side of the column.
The window and property editor are shown in a row. If you need to remove the stop icon and restore the suspended window, you only need to click the window icon in the upper right corner of the drawing library.
When you have completed the stop or remove the stop of the drawing library, this user name setting will be saved, and it will automatically work when you start the software next time.
This function only allows Colo to adapt to different work processes and help users customize their user interface.
In addition, with the update of the new drawing library, the original old drawing library will be removed.
In the new version, we are in the user customized settings.
In the new version, we apply a new shortcut and unlock feature.
After opening the user customized window setting, you can use the unlock option in the shortcut selection card.
This lock feature also supports order name and shortcut query.
You can directly enter the name keyword or complete name to search for shortcut keys.
You can directly enter the name keyword or complete name keyword or complete name keyword to search for shortcut keys.
Then press the shortcut key corresponding to the keyboard to identify it.
If you want to customize the shortcut, please try to avoid the default shortcut setting of the system.
When there is a shortcut conflict, you will see the window.
You can choose whether to replace it.
This new unlock function can help save your time.
It is highly effective when searching for specific tools, menu shortcuts, or getting shortcut options.
The 2025.2 version has made a major update to the shortcut code.
Users can now look directly at and edit all the shortcuts in the 2D window.
The sewing line will also be linked to the shortcut to ensure that the structure is exactly the same.
In the 2D window, you can see the shortcuts on the codeboard.
It automatically follows the size and shows it in all sizes.
Switch to the edit code tool.
After selecting the shortcut, you can adjust the position in the property editor.
Click on the fixed size to lock the shortcut code position.
Ensure that the position of the shortcut is the same as the codeboard.
It remains unchanged in all other sizes.
Open the length of the display line in the 2D window.
Switching the size, you can see that the distance between the shortcut and the shortcut is always unchanged.
If you need to modify it to keep the distance from another shortcut unchanged,
you can use the shortcut tool to select the shortcut.
In the property editor, click on lock.
The lock position will be changed from the start point to the end point.
You can also enter the number to change the distance.
Keep the original distance unchanged here.
Switch to other sizes.
You can see that the length of the other end point is unchanged.
Now we will close the lock.
Switch back to the edit code tool.
If you need to edit further, you can manually enter the number in the table according to the actual situation.
Please note that the input value is always calculated on the basis of the machine code.
If you need to reverse the specific size direction, you can add a comma before the number.
If you need to reverse all sizes, you can choose the opposite direction.
Use the edit sewing line tool to switch to other sizes.
You can see that the sewing line of the chest coat and the skirt white board can be seen.
If you need to edit the specific size direction, you can add a comma before the number.
The sewing lines of the chest coat and skirt white board are always perfectly aligned at the cutout.
This update has realized the linkage of all sizes of the sewing line and the cutout.
Therefore, when the chest coat is switched between different sizes, the sewing line will always follow the cutout.
This optimization improves the accuracy of the number of the number and the whole number of the board.
In the Clo2025.2 version, based on accurate 2D measurement, the placement of the drawing will become more convenient.
will become more convenient.
Use the adjustment sticker tool
to select the sticker that needs to be adjusted.
In the property editor,
you can activate the 2D measurement function based on the end point or the outer line.
This is used to operate the end point.
First, select it at the bottom.
Then you will see that there is a distance parameter at the bottom.
Its measurement value will be displayed next to the sticker within the range of the sheet.
Through this method,
you can manually enter the value,
accurately control the distance between the end point or the outer line of the sticker.
Then in the back position,
I will activate the option on the outer line of the sheet.
Enter the specified distance here to accurately locate the sticker,
so as to fully meet the requirements of the process unit.
This update makes the position of the sticker more accurate,
so that the final design is in your control.
In the 2025.2 version,
we updated the selection option of the fixing needle tool.
Now you can delete all the fixing needles on the selected sheet.
Now use the fixing needle tool.
Add fixing needles to different sheets at random.
Select any fixing needle.
Right-click.
Delete the fixing needles on the selected sheet.
In the previous version,
when selecting the fixing needles on the sheet,
there are only two options.
Delete the fixing needles selected,
or delete all the fixing needles.
Now in the latest version,
you can delete all the fixing needles on the selected sheet,
instead of deleting all the fixing needles on the entire suit.
This update provides greater flexibility for you to create 3D clothing.
Then right-click the fixing needle on any side of the sheet.
Delete the fixing needles on the selected sheet.
You can see that this fixing needle contains multiple sheets.
With this new function,
the fixing needles do not need to be deleted by the whole set,
but can be deleted by pressing the sheet.
Now switch to the selection tool.
Select any fixing needle that contains two sheets.
Double-click on the fixing needle.
Press the Delete button to delete the fixing needles on this sheet.
You can see the double-click fixing needles.
The fixing needles on the same sheet
will be all selected.
Press the Delete button to delete all the fixing needles on this sheet.
Of course, you can also use the function we used before.
Select to delete all the fixing needles.
We hope this update
will allow you to have more options
when editing the fixing needles on 3D clothing.
In the 2025.2 version,
you can choose whether to activate the sewing.
Open the sewing tool.
Add the sewing line at the neck.
Or create a random sewing line on the clothing.
Find the activation option in the property editor.
Open the simulation.
Re-select the activation sewing line.
Simulate again.
In the previous version,
once the sewing is applied,
unless you delete it,
otherwise it will always exist.
Therefore, in this version,
we have updated the sewing function.
After adding the sewing in the armhole,
you can select to stop.
Activate the sewing option.
Also,
set the tool on the virtual model.
You can also apply the activation option in the same way.
Open the tool on the virtual model.
In any position of the virtual model,
add the sewing effect.
Find the activation option in the property editor.
Open the simulation.
Re-select the activation sewing line.
Simulate again.
We hope this update
can make you more flexible in using the sewing function.
In the previous version,
only the CPU simulation supports the software model simulation.
After this update,
the software model simulation can also be used in the GPU simulation mode.
Click on the virtual model.
In the property editor,
find and activate the software model simulation option.
At this time you can see
the 3D window at the bottom right corner
will display the software model simulation icon.
When you switch from the simulation mode to the GPU mode
and re-simulate,
you will see the virtual model
as the software model starts to simulate.
When you record the software model animation in the animation editor,
this function can speed up your recording.
Please note that this function is only supported
with the Windows system of NVIDIA GPU.
I hope this update
can bring you a faster and smoother experience.
In the 2025.2 version,
you can customize the hat as a configuration.
Find the virtual model in the main menu.
Select the customized configuration.
In the pop-up window,
you will find that when you select the configuration type,
the hat option has been added.
As before,
you can import the OBJ file.
You can also customize the version as a hat.
Select all the versions of the hat.
After completing the other option settings,
click Save.
Save it as a customized configuration.
Close the prompt window.
After customizing,
you can freely add the hat to other projects.
We hope that the new configuration type
can help you explore more possibilities.
From the 2025.2 version,
MetaHuman in the UI
as a virtual model can be imported.
You can import MetaHuman
in the main menu in the main menu column
in the DNA format.
In the main menu column,
you can find the file import or import and increase.
Before importing,
please note that
to ensure that MetaHuman presents the correct skin,
your DNA file must be stored under the same path
as other postage files.
In the MetaHuman DNA import window,
click the File plus icon.
Select the corresponding MetaHuman body and head file.
You can modify various settings in the import window.
For example,
the unit and proportion of MetaHuman.
In the options,
default will automatically increase the arrangement point
and automatically create a test穿服.
You can also cancel the selection of these options.
Later,
manually increase the arrangement point and create a test穿服.
After clicking OK,
MetaHuman will be added to the workspace
and can be used as a virtual model.
In the 3D vertical menu,
you can also modify the surface type of the model under the virtual model information display.
Click on the display arrangement point
to present the arrangement point of MetaHuman.
I wish you a speedy arrangement of the version.
This function supports the import,
using the self-defined role model created by MetaHuman Creator,
to further improve the compatibility of Colour and UE.
In the 2025.2 version,
the pull chain can be copied to the version with a symmetrical relationship.
When you right-click on the pull chain,
and then select to copy to the version with symmetrical modification,
the pull chain will be copied to the other side of the version.
The pull chain after the symmetry is copied,
its material and specifications are consistent with the original pull chain.
This function can help you improve the efficiency of work,
and quickly create a symmetrical pull chain.
In the new version,
we have optimized the appearance of the pull chain,
the pull head,
and the pull out of the costume.
Now the pull chain can be activated with the version,
or it is back-activated.
This will make your operation more convenient.
When you back-activate the related version,
the pull chain will remain in the same state.
When you back-activate the version again,
you can see that the pull chain will also be activated together.
I hope this can help you simplify the operation,
and improve the efficiency of work.
2025.2 is supported in the text editor,
and the material is rotated horizontally and vertically.
No more need to rotate.
When you want to rotate vertically and vertically in text,
select it,
and click directly to rotate vertically.
You can also rotate horizontally.
You can see its effect directly in the 3D window.
Through this function,
you can create your patterns and prints more quickly and freely.
Next let's take a look at,
the optimization of the UV editor.
From this version,
you can directly,
in the window of the UV editor,
based on the same property,
quickly and accurately select the version.
First, as you can see,
there are multiple costumes in this file.
In the main menu material,
UV,
click the UV editor to open the window.
In the window of the UV editor,
you can see the version of the pull chain.
As you can see,
select the same property list to add to this place.
When the mouse is stopped on the list,
it will display purple options,
including the particle structure layer and the material.
Next, we use the material as an example,
select the version,
click it,
all versions that use the same material as the version,
will be selected at the same time in the UV editor.
Now you can easily select the version,
move to the target UV area,
or directly bake the UV,
the particle structure layer is also similar.
Next, let's take a look at another option that has been added.
Select all sewing versions,
select the sleeve version of the chain,
and right-click.
When you click this option,
all versions of the chain will be selected at the same time.
You can also use the shortcut Ctrl-Alt-A,
or directly double-click the version,
and select the sleeve version of the chain.
Now,
when you need to adjust all related versions of a specific version,
this function is very useful.
Through the above functions,
you can now quickly and accurately
divide the properties according to your needs,
so that your UV baking process is more efficient.
The following is the improved content related to animation.
After this update,
you can now apply the key needle
to more extensive properties,
including pressure-proof sewing needles,
shrinked sheets,
shape-adjusting sheets,
and accessories.
At the same time,
the usability of the animation editor has also been significantly improved,
allowing us to carefully understand the improvements.
First, when you set the key needle,
the animation editor will automatically open.
You don't need to manually open the editor.
After updating,
it can help you achieve a smoother and more intuitive workflow.
Second,
you can add multiple functions
to simplify the addition and editing of cross-layer key needles.
At the same time,
you can create key needles for multiple object layers in the scene.
Next,
you can use the costume as an example to operate.
On the timeline of the animation editor,
you will need to add the key needle position
to the playhead.
Then,
in the object layer list,
use the Ctrl key or Shift key to select multiple object layers.
Then,
you can select multiple object layers.
You can find that
in the tool bar's automatic key needle side,
a new layer has been added to the selected layer to add the key needle icon.
Click on the icon.
You can create key needles for all selected object layers at the same time.
Press and hold the icon to select the tool group.
Click on it to create a layer for all objects.
After clicking,
you will find all objects that can be set as key needles,
such as costumes,
virtual models,
controllers,
and so on,
will be added to the animation editor.
Next,
from the same tool group,
choose to add key needles for all layers.
You can create key needles for all object layers in the animation editor.
You don't need to make a choice.
Now,
let's explore
the new properties of the new key needle.
From this version,
you can create a new key needle
by simply changing the settings in the support menu.
The switch and click button that appears in the upper-right corner
are the key needle of the animation editor.
It provides a new key needle for all the object layers.
In addition,
one of the key needle is the key needle
that is in the play,
which is the key to the function.
Now,
you can graph the key needle
from the snack bar.
Click on the icon.
You can set the key binding
by clicking on the icon.
In this mode,
you can see
Click the icon again to set the final key frame.
Finally, complete the animation to adjust the quality of the simulation.
Cut to the hand frame and adjust the range of play.
Click the recording icon in the toolbar.
Play the animation after recording is complete.
You will see the smooth change of the pressure value in the 3D window.
If you need to modify the pressure value,
you can also click on the small triangle on the left side of the board to open the detailed properties,
modify the pressure value and re-set the key frame.
You can modify the ratio in the properties editor or animation editor on the left side of the board.
You can see the effect of the 3D window panel shrinkage.
About the panel shape optimization.
You can adjust whether to activate the shape optimization,
and the strength parameters of the shape optimization.
Here the initial state is for the activation of the shape solidification
In the 8th needle, the activation of the shape solidification
The 24th needle set the strength of the shape solidification to 100
You can see the final effect
About the fake needle
Also supports adjustment of the activation state
In addition, it also supports the length of the line to set the key needle
About the copy, you can freely set its weight change
As you can see, the key needle animation line supports more properties
These updates make animation editing more accurate
And have performance
Try to use these new functions
To create a more exquisite and vivid animation effect
In the previous Kolo version
When rendering a rotating picture
If you stop halfway for any reason
It is impossible to restart rendering from the stopped needle
Now from this version
You can rotate the picture
Set the start and end needles
Open the rendering window
Picture and video properties
In the image video download menu
Switch to rotating picture
After switching to rotating picture
You will see two new parts
Start needle and end needle
Now click to start rendering
If rendering stops
You can enter the starting needle
The rendering will restart from the input needle
This update will allow you to better control the rotating picture
We have released a new function
Delay and saving costs
Combined with other data performance functions
Users can now check the workflow efficiency
And the current cost saving situation
First, go to the settings page of the company layer
In the settings page, select the content
Work process
Click on the plus sign below
Add custom workflow label
Click on the end state button to set the delivery period
To determine the label represents the final step of the workflow
You can click on the hook or cancel the hook
After setting up
You can change the current workflow status label according to each 3D file
For example, when this file has been accepted by the buyer
You can change the label to the current one
From the final draft to pass
Finally, you can click on the negative data in the upper right corner
Delivery cycle
Check the delivery cycle analysis
For example, the average delivery cycle and the average delivery time
This shows the average consumption of the content in each workflow
For example, you spent an average of 13 hours
Completed the first round of draft
In addition, you can also select the selection result according to the category above
For example, we can choose clothing and men's clothing
Click on the application to select
Scroll down
You can also see the spending time of each file
After returning to the studio
You can click on the negative data saving cost in the upper right corner
To calculate the saving cost of all the content in the studio
Saving cost is based on the number of versions and color numbers of each model
The default cost calculated by user definition
Scroll down
You can also set the self-definition of each file
Saving cost
Usually, it takes 30 US dollars to make one plus class
The system will automatically calculate the current saving cost
By using a new data-saving tool
Users can automatically evaluate the cost and efficiency